Guide to the James L. Vizzard Papers, 1942-1983
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES III: NATIONAL CATHOLIC RURAL LIFE CONFERENCE, 1942-1968
  - Subseries D. Administrative Files
    - Annual Convention, Sept. 26-29, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Annual Convention, Sept. 13-16, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Annual Convention, Oct. 8-10. 1963 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Annual Convention, Aug. 27-30, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Annual Convention, Aug. 17-19 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Annual Convention, Oct. 13-16, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1954-1955, 1956, 1960, 1961, 1064. 1965, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Conclusiones de Panama; correspondence of Msgr. Ligutti concerning Rural Life Congress, Panama, Apr. 17-24, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Constitution and By-laws, 1951, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Diocesan Directors Meeting, Nov. 6, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 14-15, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 25-26, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Oct. 8-9, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 14-15, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 17-18, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 16-17, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 20-21, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 23-24, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 21-23, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 18-20, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 29-30, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 19-20, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June. 23, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 25-26, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 21-22, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 18-19, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - International Catholic Conference on Problems of Rural Life, Rome, June 25-July 2, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Meeting the Challenge of Communism in Latin America," Chile, Dec. 2-9, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Merrill Trust Fund Project, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings, 1957-1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Pamphlets, 1962, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Roster, 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Rural Life Workshop, Aug. 15-18, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Seminar for Dominican Sisters, July 13-14, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Steering Committee Report, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Washington Office activity reports, 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Washington Office financial reports, 1955-1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- SERIES IV: SOCIAL APOSTOLATE, CALIFORNIA PROVINCE, SOCIETY OF JESUS, 1968-1972
  - Subseries A. Out-Going Correspondence
    - Out-Going Correspondence Feb.-June, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Out-Going Correspondence July-Nov., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Mar.-June, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Out-Going Correspondence July-Aug., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Sept.-Oct., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Nov.-Dec., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Jan.-Feb., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Mar.-Apr., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Out-Going Correspondence May-June, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B. In-Coming Correspondence
    - Ahern-Buckley (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Campion-Curran (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Davidson-Duff (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Emerick-Frick (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ganz-Hughes (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Janda-Lorenz (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - M-Murray (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Nagle-O'Rourke (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Patch-Ryan (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Sandmeyer-Twomey (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Vaughan-Yzermans (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C. Administrative Files
    - Advisory Committee Minutes, Director's Reports, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, News Orleans, New york Jesuit Provinces, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - La Posada eviction, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Oregon Jesuit Province, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Project Equality, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Province Directors of the Social Apostolate, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Archdiocesan Pastoral Council, roster, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Social Apostolate Newsletter, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Theology of social ministry, source materials, 1967-1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- SERIES V: UNITED FARM WORKERS, 1972-1977
  - Subseries A. Out-Going Correspondence
    - Out-Going Correspondence Jan.-Oct., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Out-Going Correspondence May-July, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Jan.-Dec., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Out-Going Correspondence Jan.-Feb., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Subseries B. In-Coming Correspondence
    - Abourezk-Curtain (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Degnan-Guido (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Haberfeld-Loftis (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Mahan-O'Rourke (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Padilla-Torres (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Vasquez-Yzermans (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Subseries C. UFW Headquarters Working Papers
    - Affidavits concerning arrests of strikers, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Boycott endorsements, 1972-1974; "Boycott: A Background Perspective," 1975; "Setting Up a Boycott,' n.d. 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Coachella Strike Newsletter, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Gallo Wines Boycott, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Mailing lists, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda, Jan.-June, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda, July-Aug., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, Sept.-Nov., 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters from Delano, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters printed by UFW support groups, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Report on Illegal Farm Labor Activity in California and Arizona," Sept., 1974; Summary of Documentation of Illegals," July, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Safeway Stores Boycott, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Subseries D. Subject files
    - AFL-CIO, 1973-1975 17 2 Bishops' Ad Hoc Committee on Farm Labor, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Center of Concern, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "A Day Without Sunshine" (television script), n.d. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Farmworker health and sanitation, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Free Marketing Council, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Labor Day Sunday, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Migrant Legal Action Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - National Conference of Catholic Bishops, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - National Conference on Land Reform, 1973; National Land for People, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - National Council of Churches, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - National Farm Worker Ministry; 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - National Farm Work Ministry, 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - National Farm Workers Health Group, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters and statements on UFW Strike, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity Migrant Programs, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Pesticides, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Rural America/Rural Housing Alliance, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - United States Catholic Conference, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, OSHA Standards Advisory Committee on Agriculture, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E. Legislative files
    - California legislative materials and court cases, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - California Proposition 22 (Farm Labor Initiative), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Federal legislative materials, miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 632 (child labor), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 982 (illegal aliens), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - House Committee on Education and Labor, Subcommittee on Agricultural Labor, Hearings on Migrants, Miami, Apr., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Other state legislative materials and court cases, 1972-1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - P.L. 93-355 (Legal Services Corporation Act), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Subseries F. Publicity files
    - Msgr. George G. Higgins, ed., "The Yardstick," Feb.-Nov., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Msgr. George G. Higgins, Mar., 1974,-June, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Jan., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Feb., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, March., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Apr., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, May, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, June, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, July, 1973 (1) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, July, 1973 (2) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Aug., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Sept., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Oct.-Nov., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Dec., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Jan., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Feb., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Mar., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Apr., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, May, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, June, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, July, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Aug., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Sept., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Oct., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Nov., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Dec., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Jan., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Feb., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Mar., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Apr., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, May, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, June, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, July, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Aug., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Sept., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Oct., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Nov., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Dec., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Jan., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Feb., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Mar., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Apr., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, May-June, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Sept.-Dec., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Newsclippings and press releases, Jan.-Mar., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- SERIES VI: SUBJECT FILES, 1953-1977
  - Subseries A. General, 1955-1975
    - "Agriculture in California," (pastoral letter), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Agriculture, Occupational group Order in (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - America Magazine, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - American Country Life Association, 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1956-1965 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - American Federation of Labor (AFL-CIO), 1961-1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Henry Pope, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bennett, Dana, 1956-1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bishops' Committee for Migrant Workers, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bishops' Committee for Migrant Workers, 1963-1966 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bishops' Committee for the Spanish Speaking, 1958-1963 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bishops' Committee for the Spanish Speaking, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Dan (Wheat Germ Flour), 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Catholic Association for International Peace, correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Catholic Association for International Peace, reports and minutes, 1956-1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - California Center for Community Development, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - California Farmer-Consumer Information Committee, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Catholic colleges, agricultural economics, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Catholic Relief Services, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Catholic Youth Encyclopedia, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - CBS Radio, 1956-1962 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Celamex Mexican Labor Center, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Church Peace Union, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty, correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty, Commission on Rural Affairs, minutes and reports, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Clergy-Economic Foundation, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Collective Bargaining, National Labor Relations Board, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Immigration from Japan, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Committee for International Economic Growth, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Community Action, Southold Town, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Consumer Assembly, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Conroy, Rev. James, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cooperative Bargaining for American Agriculture," comments, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cooperative League of the USA, 1956-1966 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cooperative League of the USA, Cooperative Modern Management Institute, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Country Beautiful Magazine, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Country Life Commission, 1958-1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Cronin, Rev. John F., "Catholic Rural Philosophy," 1958 22 16 Crowley, Msgr. Joseph R., 1962-1966 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Dartmouth Talk, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Duff, Edward, S.J., 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Edwards, Dr. Lena, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Family Farm Policy Review, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Farmers Union, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Fellabeen, by Fr. Ayrout, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Figlino, Rev. Roy, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Food For Freedom, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Food For India, Joint Resolution, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Food Stamp Plan, 1956, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Food Stamp Program, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Food-Population. Material for talks at Purdue University and St. Charles Seminary, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Food. World Food Congress, 1963, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Food. World Food Crisis article for Journal, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Aid, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Aid, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Foreign trade, materials and testimony, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Fund for Asia, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Garin Company, 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ginder, Fr. Richard, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Hermes, Mrs. Ambrose, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Hylden, Rev. Joseph, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Social Order, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - International Conference on Water for Peace, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - International Development Conference, 1965, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Joseph M., 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Jubilee Magazine, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - LaFarge Institute, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Lucey, Archbshp. Robert E., 1957-1967 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Miller, Dr. Raymond and Robert Miller, 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Minimum Wage, notes, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Money and Banking, notes, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Mulloy, Bshp. William T., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Mutual Security, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - National Advisory Commission on Rural Poverty, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor, 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - National Association for Community Development, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - National Campaign for Agricultural Democracy, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - National Catholic Social Action Conference, 1960-1966 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1955-1958 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - National Committee for Children and Youth, 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - National Committee on Natural Resources, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - National Committee on World Food Crisis, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - National conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1958-1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - National conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - National conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - National Conference on Religion and Race, Chicago, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - National Consumers League, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - National Council of Catholic Men, 1955-1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - National Council of Catholic, 1956-1967 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - National Council of Churches, 1955-1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, 1956-1972 25 12 National Farmers Union, 1955-1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - National Farmers Union, 1962-1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - National Federation of Catholic College Students, 1961-1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - National Rural Electric Cooperative Association, 1961-1967 26 3 National Service Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - National Sharecroppers Fund, 1956-1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Nunan, Ray, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, Legal Services, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity, STAR Project, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Papal Statements, 1954-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Papal Volunteers for Latin American, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Patterson, Col. Robert M., 1962 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Pay television, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Peace Corp, Citizens Sabbatical, correspondence 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Peace Corp, Citizens Sabbatical, drafts, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Peace Corps, miscellaneous, 1961-1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Population, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Poverty, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Poverty in the Southwest Conference, Aug.-Dec., 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Poverty in the Southwest Conference, Jan., 1965-Jan., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Poverty in the Southwest Conference, publicity, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Publication requests, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Religion and Labor Council of America, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Ruiz, Dr. Samuel, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Rural Poverty, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Sacco, Dr. Paul, 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - School Milk Program, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Seasonal farm Labor, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Self-Help, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Society for International Development, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Soil Conservation, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Southern Pacific Company, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Stern Family Fund, 1964-1967 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Sullivan, Leonor K., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Surpluses, 1950-1955 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Synagogue Council of America, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - United Automobile Workers (AFL-CIO), 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1955-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, Rural Areas Development Program, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Department of Commerce, 1964-1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, Demonstration Cities Program, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Department of State, 1955-1968 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives, correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Senate, correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Senate, correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Senate, correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Senate, correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Senate Bill 3683/House Bill 12121, Area Development Act, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Senate Bills 521, 522, 523, 524, 525, 526, 2877, introduced by Sen. Harrison A. Williams, 1963, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Senate Bill 109, Agricultural Producers Marketing Act, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - University of Santa Clara, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Vega, 1961-1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Vekemans, Roger, S.J., 1958-1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Washington Seminar for Theological Students, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Western States Water and Power Consumers Conference, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - White House, correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B. Delano Grape Strike, 1965-1967
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, (with news media), 1966 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters and press releases, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Press coverage, 1965-1967 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Willinger, Bshp. Aloysius controversy, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Subseries C. Farm Labor Contractors Registration Act, 1964-1976
    - Background materials and notes, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Background materials and notes, 1973-Feb., 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Background materials and notes, Mar.-June, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Background materials and notes, July, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Background materials and notes (1), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Background materials and notes (2), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Subseries D. Migrants, 1953-1967
    - "Harvest of Shame" (television script), Nov. 25, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, 1953-1957 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Migrant case histories, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1)